Guide to the American Committee for Cultural Freedom Records TAM.023
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series III: American Committee for Cultural Freedom
  - Subseries J: Miscellaneous
    - Kalmuck Resettlement Committee see also, Tamiment collection# 29, Kalmuck Resettlement Committee Records, 1950-51, 0.5 linear feet, 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - International Conference of Contemporary Music, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Facts Forum, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Subseries K: Clippings
    - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Jan 1953-Mar 1953 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Apr 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Jan 1954-Sep 1954 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Oct 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Jan 1955-Feb 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Mar 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Jan 1956-Mar 1956 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Apr 1956-Oct 1956 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Nov 1956-Dec 1956 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Restricted Material: Consult with Archives Staff.
  - Ceylon, 1952-1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Fund Raising Campaign, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Jacobs, Norman: Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Jacobs, Paul: Allegations re Daniel Bell, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Leontief, Vassily: Loyalty Case, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - McCarthy and the Communists: Beacon Press Contract & Correspondence, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Pro Musica Antiqua Case (Tour Cancellation), 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Stein, Sol: Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Terzian, James, Case (Security), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Williams, William Carlos, Case (Loyalty), 1954 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Wolfe, Bertram: Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Woodcock, George, Case (Visa Denial), 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 12)